My Secret Valentine is a tv movie, romance film directed by Bradley Walsh.
A young woman takes advice from the chalkboard notes that her mysterious house rental tenant
leaves when a slick sales rep arrives with plans to buy her family’s prized winery.
Chloe Grange, played by Lacey Chabert.
Seth Anderson, played by Andrew W. Walker.
Truman Grange, played by Peter MacNeill.
Leanne Morrison, played by Tara Yelland.
Taylor, played by Cindy Sampson.
Maggie, played by Catherine Burdon.
My Bloody Valentine is a 1981 Canadian slasher film directed by
George Mihalka from a screenplay by John Beaird.
It features an ensemble cast that includes Paul
Kelman, Lori Hallier, and Neil Affleck.
The plot tells about a group of young adults who decide to throw a Valentine's Day party, only to
incur the vengeful wrath of a maniac in mining gear who begins a killing spree.
Conceived and produced entirely over the course of around a year, the film was
shot on location in Sydney Mines, Nova Scotia, in the fall of 1980.
It was theatrically released in Canadian theaters on February 13, 1981, by
Paramount Pictures Corporation, coinciding with the Valentine's holiday.
Despite a mixed response from critics and grossing $5.7 million at the box office, the
film has developed a large cult following over the years since its release.
My Bloody Valentine faced notable censorship, having a total of nine minutes cut by the
Motion Picture Association of America due to the amount of violence and gore.
Though co-producer Dunning confirmed that the excised footage still existed, attempts to
release it proved difficult as Paramount Pictures refused to offer an uncut version.
In 2009, Lionsgate subsequently licensed the home media rights to the film and released
Blu-ray and DVD editions with three minutes of additional footage restored.
The same year, Lionsgate released a remake of the film.
The tone is emotional.